<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Fatih Uenal</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Fatih Uenal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 12:14:34 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Honeynet - Simulating Real-World Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-5/</guid>
      <description>Project Details The primary goal of this project involved establishing intentionally vulnerable virtual machines within the Azure infrastructure, as detailed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring and Implementing a Honeypot in Azure</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-6/</guid>
      <description>Project Details To initiate the commencement of my Azure Honeynet project, the initial step involves configuring the virtual machines (VMs) that will be utilized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Incident Analysis Using SQL</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-7/</guid>
      <description>Project Details The objective of these situations is to evaluate my competency in utilizing SQL for data analysis and addressing problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Management with OpenVAS</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-8/</guid>
      <description>Project Details In this project, a secure Azure network was created and populated with two virtual machines, set to run OpenVAS Vulnerability Management Scanner and Windows 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NLP pipeline for text-classification</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Project Details This application is based on an Artificial Neural Network model to classify policy texts using data from various sources such as news-articles and official government databases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AI and Data Science in climate policy research</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Project Details At the University of Oxford, I present how we use AI and Data Science to accelerate and improve the policy research and advocacy work at the Fossil Fuel Non-Proliferation Treaty Initiative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XGBoost prediction on European energy preferences</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Project Details In this full-stack data science project for the University of Geneva, I used XGBoost in python to distill the most important features in predicting fossil fuel taxtation preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global fossil fuel policy tracker application</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Project Details The objective of the Fossil Fuel Non-Proliferation Tracker is to identify, gather, filter, categorise and visualise supply-side policies on a global scale, while also providing granular insight within each country on the actors involved in furthering supply-side policies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>